const data = [
    {
      question: "28+35+22+15",                                   //     1
      a: "80",
      b: "90",
      c: "70",
      d: "100",
      correct: "100",
    },
    {
      question: "81+22+19+37+18+33",                          //    2
      a: "200",
      b: "190",
      c: "220",
      d: "210",
      correct: "210",
    },
    {
      question: "94+95+63+76+25+137",          //                3
      a: "470",
      b: "490",
      c: "480",
      d: "500",
      correct: "490",
    },
    {
      question: "692603-243497+720002-362701",                       //4 
      a: "906307",
      b: "906327",
      c: "806317",
      d: "806307",
      correct: "806307",
    },
    {
      question: "200000-198545+700000-699754",                 //5
      a: "1801",
      b: "1001",
      c: "1701",
      d: "1901",
      correct: "1001",
    },
    {
      question: "60718+5967+20016-9324",                        //6
      a: "77387",
      b: "77377",
      c: "87376",
      d: "806307",
      correct: "77377",
    },
    {
      question: "Manfiy sonlar berilgan qatorni toping. 1)-1/4, -2.5/3, 6, 0; 2)1/4, 8.7/9,6,17,19; 3)-5,-2.7/15,-19,-26; 4)5,4,3,2,1; 5)10,11,12,13,...",
      a: "1;4",                         //7
      b: "4;5",
      c: "1",
      d: "3",
      correct: "3",
    },
    {
      question: "Manfiy sonlar berilgan qatorni toping. 1)-77,-66,-44; 2)2,5,6,17,19; 3)0,-33,-44,-55; 4)-4,-23/36,-16,-44; 5)10,11,12,13,...",
      a: "1;3",           //8
      b: "1;4",
      c: "1;3;4",
      d: "5",
      correct: "1;4",
    },
    {
      question: "Manfiy sonlar berilgan qatorni toping. 1)10,11,12,13,...; 2)2,5,6,17,19; 3)-4,13/14,16,-44; 4)-3,-2018,-55; 5)-1,-6,-44",
      a: "4;5",                       //9
      b: "3;4;5",
      c: "2;4;5",
      d: "3",
      correct: "4;5",
    },
    {
      question: "Musbat sonlar berilgan qatorni toping. 1)1/4,-2.3/5,6,0; 2)1/4,5.9/76,0; 3)-5,-2.7/15,-19,-26; 4)5,4,3,2,1/7; 5)10,11,12,13,...",
      a: "1;4",                        //10
      b: "4;5",
      c: "1;3",
      d: "2",
      correct: "4;5",
    },
    {
      question: "Musbat sonlar berilgan qatorni toping. 1)3.5/41,2,6; 2)1/4,-2.17/59,-6; 3)-2,-94/8,-14,26; 4)5,4,3,2,1/7; 5)-22,-33,-44",
      a: "1;4",                             //11
      b: "4;5",
      c: "2;4;5",
      d: "4",
      correct: "1;4",
    },
    {
      question: "Musbat sonlar berilgan qatorni toping. 1)17/44, 42.3/5,8; 2)1/4,3.2/5,78; 3)19,32.17/35,-19,-26; 4)5,43,-2.1/7 5)11,22,-33,44,...",
      a: "1;4",             //12
      b: "3;5",
      c: "1;2",
      d: "3",
      correct: "1;2",
    },
    {
      question: "-69-88 ni hisoblang.",
      a: "-127",
      b: "-137",                   //13
      c: "-147",
      d: "-157",
      correct: "-157",
    },
    {
      question: "-76-29 ni hisoblang.",
      a: "-122",
      b: "-132",          //14
      c: "-142",
      d: "-152",
      correct: "-122",
    }]

    export default data